(Bermadette:)Strike two.
(Howard:)I'm copying Leonard.
(Howard:)When he does this to Penny,
they have sex and watch Monty Python.
-Howard!
-I know. It was dumb.
(Howard:)I shouldn't have done it.
And it's making me feel sad.
(Howard:)So sad.
(Howard:)You know, why don't you take a bath?
I'll do the dishes.
(Raj:)Three, two, one...
(Sheldon:)That's it.
(Stuart:)Our dating profiles are live
on the Internet.
Attention all shoppers:
my business is open for business!
(Stuart:)That's right, ladies.
(Stuart:)For all you know,
I'm confident and fun to be around.
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
(Raj:)Oh, cool, it tells you
when someone's reading your profile.
"Jenny309."
(Raj:)I hope that's not her weight.
If it is, I'll... I'll take her.